[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0312_0101_shadowscastfinalsalute",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0312_0101_d_00_container_shadowscastfinalsalute",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0312_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "03_Quest_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0312_0101_shadowscastfinalsalute_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0312_0101_shadowscastfinalsalute_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0312_0101_shadowscastfinalsalute_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0312_0101_shadowscastfinalsalute_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0312_0101_shadowscastfinalsalute_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0312_0101_shadowscastfinalsalute_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0312_0101_shadowscastfinalsalute_complete_available_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "GreatCleaveArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0316_0101_maliceaforethought",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0316_0101_d_00_container_maliceaforethought",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0316_Warden",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "03_Quest_02",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0316_0101_maliceaforethought_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0316_0101_maliceaforethought_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0316_0101_maliceaforethought_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0316_0101_maliceaforethought_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0316_0101_maliceaforethought_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0316_0101_maliceaforethought_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0316_0101_maliceaforethought_complete_available_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "GreatCleaveArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0313_0101_descentfrostedslumber",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0313_0101_d_00_container_descentfrostedslumber",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0313_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "03_Quest_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "03_Quest_02",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0313_0101_descentfrostedslumber_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0313_0101_descentfrostedslumber_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0313_0101_descentfrostedslumber_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0313_0101_descentfrostedslumber_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0313_0101_descentfrostedslumber_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0313_0101_descentfrostedslumber_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0313_0101_descentfrostedslumber_complete_available_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "GreatCleaveArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0312_0201_allnottornasunder",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0312_0201_d_00_container_allnottornasunder",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0316_Warden",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "03_Quest_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "03_Quest_02",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0312_0201_allnottornasunder_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0312_0201_allnottornasunder_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0312_0201_allnottornasunder_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0312_0201_allnottornasunder_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0312_0201_allnottornasunder_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0312_0201_allnottornasunder_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0312_0201_allnottornasunder_complete_available_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "GreatCleaveArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0318_0101_facetslightdarkness",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0318_0101_d_00_container_facetslightdarkness",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0318_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "03_Quest_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "QuestUnlock_SextonComplete",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0318_0101_facetslightdarkness_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0318_0101_facetslightdarkness_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0318_0101_facetslightdarkness_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0318_0101_facetslightdarkness_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0318_0101_facetslightdarkness_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0318_0101_facetslightdarkness_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0318_0101_facetslightdarkness_complete_available_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "GreatCleaveArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0313_0102_transmuteirontodust",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0313_0102_d_00_container_transmuteirontodust",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0313_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "03_Quest_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "03_Quest_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0313_0102_transmuteirontodust_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0313_0102_transmuteirontodust_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0313_0102_transmuteirontodust_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0313_0102_transmuteirontodust_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0313_0102_transmuteirontodust_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0313_0102_transmuteirontodust_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0313_0102_transmuteirontodust_complete_available_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "GreatCleaveArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0313_0201_redefiningboundaries",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0313_0201_d_00_container_redefiningboundaries",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0313_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "03_Quest_07",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "03_Quest_05",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0313_0201_redefiningboundaries_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0313_0201_redefiningboundaries_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0313_0201_redefiningboundaries_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0313_0201_redefiningboundaries_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0313_0201_redefiningboundaries_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0313_0201_redefiningboundaries_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0313_0201_redefiningboundaries_complete_available_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "GreatCleaveArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0316_0201_tiesthatblind",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0316_0201_d_00_container_tiesthatblind",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0317_Warden",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "03_Quest_08",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "03_Quest_07",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0316_0201_tiesthatblind_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0316_0201_tiesthatblind_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0316_0201_tiesthatblind_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0316_0201_tiesthatblind_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0316_0201_tiesthatblind_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0316_0201_tiesthatblind_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0316_0201_tiesthatblind_complete_available_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "GreatCleaveArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0317_0101_forarainyday",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0317_0101_d_00_container_forarainyday",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0317_Warden",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "03_Quest_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "03_Quest_08",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0317_0101_forarainyday_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0317_0101_forarainyday_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0317_0101_forarainyday_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0317_0101_forarainyday_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0317_0101_forarainyday_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0317_0101_forarainyday_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0317_0101_forarainyday_complete_available_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "GreatCleaveArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0319_0101_rainbowheartshadowintent",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0319_0101_d_00_container_rainbowheartshadowintent",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0319_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "03_Quest_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "03_Quest_05",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0319_0101_rainbowheartshadowintent_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0319_0101_rainbowheartshadowintent_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0319_0101_rainbowheartshadowintent_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0319_0101_rainbowheartshadowintent_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0319_0101_rainbowheartshadowintent_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0319_0101_rainbowheartshadowintent_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0319_0101_rainbowheartshadowintent_complete_available_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "GreatCleaveArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0315_0101_aburningquestion",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0315_0101_d_00_container_aburningquestion",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0315_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "03_Quest_11",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "03_Quest_09",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0315_0101_aburningquestion_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0315_0101_aburningquestion_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0315_0101_aburningquestion_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0315_0101_aburningquestion_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0315_0101_aburningquestion_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0315_0101_aburningquestion_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0315_0101_aburningquestion_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0314_0101_blessingsofthefallen",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0314_0101_d_00_container_blessingsofthefallen",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0314_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "03_Quest_12",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "03_Quest_09",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0314_0101_blessingsofthefallen_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0314_0101_blessingsofthefallen_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0314_0101_blessingsofthefallen_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0314_0101_blessingsofthefallen_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0314_0101_blessingsofthefallen_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0314_0101_blessingsofthefallen_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0314_0101_blessingsofthefallen_complete_available_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "GreatCleaveArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0315_0102_twistedmetamorphosis",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0315_0102_d_00_container_twistedmetamorphosis",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0315_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "03_Quest_13",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "03_Quest_11",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0315_0102_twistedmetamorphosis_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0315_0102_twistedmetamorphosis_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0315_0102_twistedmetamorphosis_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0315_0102_twistedmetamorphosis_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0315_0102_twistedmetamorphosis_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0315_0102_twistedmetamorphosis_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0315_0102_twistedmetamorphosis_complete_available_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "GreatCleaveArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0314_0102_thebestofus",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0314_0102_d_00_container_thebestofus",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0314_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "03_Quest_14",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "03_Quest_13",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0314_0102_thebestofus_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0314_0102_thebestofus_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0314_0102_thebestofus_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0314_0102_thebestofus_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0314_0102_thebestofus_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0314_0102_thebestofus_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0314_0102_thebestofus_complete_available_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "GreatCleaveArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0317_0201_windingmtnpath",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 50,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0317_0201_d_00_container_windingmtnpath",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1416_Warden",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "03_Quest_15",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "03_Quest_14",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0317_0201_windingmtnpath_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0317_0201_windingmtnpath_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0317_0201_windingmtnpath_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0317_0201_windingmtnpath_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0317_0201_windingmtnpath_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0317_0201_windingmtnpath_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0317_0201_windingmtnpath_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0319_0501_PrimeResolve",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0319_0501_d_00_Containter_weaponwrapperquest",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0719_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_PrimeResolve_00",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "07_Quest_11",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0319_0501_PrimeResolve_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0319_0501_a_Title",
        "Description": "@0319_0501_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0319_0501_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0319_0501_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0319_0501_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0319_0501_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0319_0502_PROne",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0319_0501_d_01_01_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete1",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_PrimeResolve_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0319_0502_PROneSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0319_0502_a_Title",
        "Description": "@0319_0502_b_Description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0319_0503_PRTwo",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0319_0501_d_01_02_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete2",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_PrimeResolve_02",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0319_0503_PRTwoSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0319_0503_a_Title",
        "Description": "@0319_0503_b_Description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0319_0504_PRThree",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0319_0501_d_01_03_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete3",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_PrimeResolve_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0319_0504_PRThreeSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0319_0504_a_Title",
        "Description": "@0319_0504_b_Description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0319_0505_PRFour",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0319_0501_d_01_04_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete4",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_PrimeResolve_04",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0319_0505_PRFourSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0319_0505_a_Title",
        "Description": "@0319_0505_b_Description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0319_0506_PRFive",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0319_0501_d_02_01_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete1",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_PrimeResolve_05",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0319_0506_PRFiveSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0319_0506_a_Title",
        "Description": "@0319_0506_b_Description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0319_0507_PRSix",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0319_0501_d_02_02_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete2",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_PrimeResolve_06",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0319_0507_PRSixSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0319_0507_a_Title",
        "Description": "@0319_0507_b_Description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0319_0508_PRSeven",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0319_0501_d_02_03_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete3",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_PrimeResolve_07",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0319_0508_PRSevenSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0319_0508_a_Title",
        "Description": "@0319_0508_b_Description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0319_0509_PREight",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0319_0501_d_02_04_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete4",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_PrimeResolve_08",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0319_0509_PREightSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0319_0509_a_Title",
        "Description": "@0319_0509_b_Description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0320_0101_GlimmeringMercy",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0320_0101_d_00_container_GlimmeringMercy",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0719_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_GimmeringMercy_00",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "07_Quest_11",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0320_0101_GlimmeringMercy_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0320_0101_GlimmeringMercy_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0320_0101_GlimmeringMercy_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0320_0101_GlimmeringMercy_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0320_0101_GlimmeringMercy_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0320_0101_GlimmeringMercy_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0320_0101_GlimmeringMercy_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0320_0102_Prelude",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0320_0102_d_00_container_Prelude",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_GimmeringMercy_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0320_0102_Prelude_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0320_0102_Prelude_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0320_0102_Prelude_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0320_0102_Prelude_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0320_0102_Prelude_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0320_0102_Prelude_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0320_0103_Adagio",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0320_0103_d_00_container_Adagio",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_GimmeringMercy_02",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0320_0103_Adagio_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0320_0103_Adagio_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0320_0103_Adagio_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0320_0103_Adagio_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0320_0103_Adagio_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0320_0103_Adagio_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0320_0104_Scherzo",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0320_0104_d_00_container_Scherzo",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_GimmeringMercy_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0320_0104_Scherzo_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0320_0104_Scherzo_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0320_0104_Scherzo_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0320_0104_Scherzo_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0320_0104_Scherzo_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0320_0104_Scherzo_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0320_0105_Shanty",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0320_0105_d_00_container_Shanty",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_GimmeringMercy_04",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0320_0105_Shanty_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0320_0105_Shanty_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0320_0105_Shanty_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0320_0105_Shanty_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0320_0105_Shanty_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0320_0105_Shanty_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0320_0106_Zarabanda",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0320_0106_d_00_container_Zarabanda",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_GimmeringMercy_05",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0320_0106_Zarabanda_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0320_0106_Zarabanda_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0320_0106_Zarabanda_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0320_0106_Zarabanda_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0320_0106_Zarabanda_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0320_0106_Zarabanda_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0320_0107_Requiem",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0320_0107_d_00_container_Requiem",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_GimmeringMercy_06",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0320_0107_Requiem_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0320_0107_Requiem_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0320_0107_Requiem_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0320_0107_Requiem_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0320_0107_Requiem_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0320_0107_Requiem_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0320_0108_Passepied",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0320_0108_d_00_container_Passepied",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_GimmeringMercy_07",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0320_0108_Passepied_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0320_0108_Passepied_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0320_0108_Passepied_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0320_0108_Passepied_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0320_0108_Passepied_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0320_0108_Passepied_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0320_0109_Sonata",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0320_0109_d_00_container_Sonata",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_GimmeringMercy_08",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0320_0109_Sonata_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0320_0109_Sonata_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0320_0109_Sonata_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0320_0109_Sonata_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0320_0109_Sonata_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0320_0109_Sonata_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0321_0101_AzureRavager",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0321_0101_d_00_container_AzureRavager",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0719_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_AzureRavager_00",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "07_Quest_11",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0321_0101_AzureRavager_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0321_0101_AzureRavager_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0321_0101_AzureRavager_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0321_0101_AzureRavager_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0321_0101_AzureRavager_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0321_0101_AzureRavager_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0321_0101_AzureRavager_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0321_0102_AzureRavager_deathandtaxes",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0321_0102_d_00_container_AzureRavager_deathandtaxes",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_AzureRavager_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0321_0102_AzureRavager_deathandtaxes_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0321_0102_AzureRavager_deathandtaxes_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0321_0102_AzureRavager_deathandtaxes_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0321_0102_AzureRavager_deathandtaxes_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0321_0102_AzureRavager_deathandtaxes_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0321_0102_AzureRavager_deathandtaxes_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0321_0103_AzureRavager_byrootandbough",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0321_0103_d_00_container_AzureRavager_byrootandbough",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_AzureRavager_02",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0321_0103_AzureRavager_byrootandbough_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0321_0103_AzureRavager_byrootandbough_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0321_0103_AzureRavager_byrootandbough_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0321_0103_AzureRavager_byrootandbough_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0321_0103_AzureRavager_byrootandbough_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0321_0103_AzureRavager_byrootandbough_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0321_0104_AzureRavager_sampleofevil",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0321_0104_d_00_container_AzureRavager_sampleofevil",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_AzureRavager_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0321_0104_AzureRavager_sampleofevil_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0321_0104_AzureRavager_sampleofevil_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0321_0104_AzureRavager_sampleofevil_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0321_0104_AzureRavager_sampleofevil_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0321_0104_AzureRavager_sampleofevil_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0321_0104_AzureRavager_sampleofevil_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0321_0105_AzureRavager_crystalcorruption",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0321_0105_d_00_container_AzureRavager_crystalcorruption",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_AzureRavager_04",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0321_0105_AzureRavager_crystalcorruption_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0321_0105_AzureRavager_crystalcorruption_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0321_0105_AzureRavager_crystalcorruption_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0321_0105_AzureRavager_crystalcorruption_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0321_0105_AzureRavager_crystalcorruption_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0321_0105_AzureRavager_crystalcorruption_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0321_0106_AzureRavager_shardsaboveandbelow",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0321_0106_d_00_container_AzureRavager_shardsaboveandbelow",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0719_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_AzureRavager_05",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0321_0106_AzureRavager_shardsaboveandbelow_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0321_0106_AzureRavager_shardsaboveandbelow_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0321_0106_AzureRavager_shardsaboveandbelow_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0321_0106_AzureRavager_shardsaboveandbelow_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0321_0106_AzureRavager_shardsaboveandbelow_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0321_0106_AzureRavager_shardsaboveandbelow_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0321_0107_AzureRavager_woodenheartsironheads",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0321_0107_d_00_container_AzureRavager_woodenheartsironheads",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_AzureRavager_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "0321_0106_AzureRavager_shardsaboveandbelow",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0321_0107_AzureRavager_woodenheartsironheads_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0321_0107_AzureRavager_woodenheartsironheads_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0321_0107_AzureRavager_woodenheartsironheads_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0321_0107_AzureRavager_woodenheartsironheads_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0321_0107_AzureRavager_woodenheartsironheads_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0321_0107_AzureRavager_woodenheartsironheads_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0321_0108_AzureRavager_stickingtotheplan",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0321_0108_d_00_container_AzureRavager_stickingtotheplan",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_AzureRavager_07",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0321_0108_AzureRavager_stickingtotheplan_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0321_0108_AzureRavager_stickingtotheplan_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0321_0108_AzureRavager_stickingtotheplan_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0321_0108_AzureRavager_stickingtotheplan_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0321_0108_AzureRavager_stickingtotheplan_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0321_0108_AzureRavager_stickingtotheplan_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0321_0109_AzureRavager_gleamingedge",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0321_0109_d_00_container_AzureRavager_gleamingedge",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0321_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_AzureRavager_08",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0321_0109_AzureRavager_gleamingedge_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0321_0109_AzureRavager_gleamingedge_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0321_0109_AzureRavager_gleamingedge_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0321_0109_AzureRavager_gleamingedge_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0321_0109_AzureRavager_gleamingedge_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0321_0109_AzureRavager_gleamingedge_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0318_0201_RampantConviction",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0318_0201_d_00_container_RampantConviction",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0719_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RampantConviction_00",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "07_Quest_11",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0318_0201_RampantConviction_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0318_0201_RampantConviction_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0318_0201_RampantConviction_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0318_0201_RampantConviction_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0318_0201_RampantConviction_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0318_0201_RampantConviction_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0318_0201_RampantConviction_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0318_0202_RampantConviction_unbalancedscales",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0318_0202_d_00_container_RampantConviction_unbalancedscales",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RampantConviction_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0318_0202_RampantConviction_unbalancedscales_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0318_0202_RampantConviction_unbalancedscales_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0318_0202_RampantConviction_unbalancedscales_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0318_0202_RampantConviction_unbalancedscales_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0318_0202_RampantConviction_unbalancedscales_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0318_0202_RampantConviction_unbalancedscales_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0318_0203_RampantConviction_piercingtheveil",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0318_0203_d_00_container_RampantConviction_piercingtheveil",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RampantConviction_02",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0318_0203_RampantConviction_piercingtheveil_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0318_0203_RampantConviction_piercingtheveil_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0318_0203_RampantConviction_piercingtheveil_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0318_0203_RampantConviction_piercingtheveil_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0318_0203_RampantConviction_piercingtheveil_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0318_0203_RampantConviction_piercingtheveil_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0318_0204_RampantConviction_bonesoftheancients",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0318_0204_d_00_container_RampantConviction_bonesoftheancients",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RampantConviction_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0318_0204_RampantConviction_bonesoftheancients_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0318_0204_RampantConviction_bonesoftheancients_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0318_0204_RampantConviction_bonesoftheancients_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0318_0204_RampantConviction_bonesoftheancients_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0318_0204_RampantConviction_bonesoftheancients_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0318_0204_RampantConviction_bonesoftheancients_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0318_0205_RampantConviction_forestsheart",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0318_0205_d_00_container_RampantConviction_forestsheart",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RampantConviction_04",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0318_0205_RampantConviction_forestsheart_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0318_0205_RampantConviction_forestsheart_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0318_0205_RampantConviction_forestsheart_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0318_0205_RampantConviction_forestsheart_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0318_0205_RampantConviction_forestsheart_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0318_0205_RampantConviction_forestsheart_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0318_0206_RampantConviction_filamentandfirmament",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0318_0206_d_00_container_RampantConviction_filamentandfirmament",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RampantConviction_05",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0318_0206_RampantConviction_filamentandfirmament_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0318_0206_RampantConviction_filamentandfirmament_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0318_0206_RampantConviction_filamentandfirmament_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0318_0206_RampantConviction_filamentandfirmament_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0318_0206_RampantConviction_filamentandfirmament_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0318_0206_RampantConviction_filamentandfirmament_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0318_0207_RampantConviction_intoburningdepths",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0318_0207_d_00_container_RampantConviction_intoburningdepths",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RampantConviction_06",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0318_0207_RampantConviction_intoburningdepths_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0318_0207_RampantConviction_intoburningdepths_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0318_0207_RampantConviction_intoburningdepths_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0318_0207_RampantConviction_intoburningdepths_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0318_0207_RampantConviction_intoburningdepths_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0318_0207_RampantConviction_intoburningdepths_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0318_0208_RampantConviction_avileharvest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0318_0208_d_00_container_RampantConviction_avileharvest",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RampantConviction_07",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0318_0208_RampantConviction_avileharvest_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0318_0208_RampantConviction_avileharvest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0318_0208_RampantConviction_avileharvest_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0318_0208_RampantConviction_avileharvest_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0318_0208_RampantConviction_avileharvest_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0318_0208_RampantConviction_avileharvest_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0318_0209_RampantConviction_thelivingcrystal",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0318_0209_d_00_container_RampantConviction_thelivingcrystal",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0318_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RampantConviction_08",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0318_0209_RampantConviction_thelivingcrystal_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0318_0209_RampantConviction_thelivingcrystal_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0318_0209_RampantConviction_thelivingcrystal_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0318_0209_RampantConviction_thelivingcrystal_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0318_0209_RampantConviction_thelivingcrystal_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0318_0209_RampantConviction_thelivingcrystal_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0325_0101_RL_00",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0325_0101_RL_00_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0719_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Rimelash_00",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "07_Quest_11",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0325_0101_RL_00_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0325_0101_RL_00_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0325_0101_RL_00_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0325_0101_RL_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0325_0101_RL_00_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0325_0101_RL_00_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0325_0101_RL_00_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0325_0102_RL_01",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0325_0102_RL_01_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Rimelash_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0325_0102_RL_01_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0325_0101_RL_01_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0325_0101_RL_01_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0325_0103_RL_02",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0325_0103_RL_02_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Rimelash_02",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0325_0103_RL_02_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0325_0101_RL_02_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0325_0101_RL_02_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0325_0104_RL_03",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0325_0104_RL_03_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Rimelash_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0325_0104_RL_03_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0325_0101_RL_03_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0325_0101_RL_03_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0325_0105_RL_04",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0325_0105_RL_04_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Rimelash_04",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0325_0105_RL_04_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0325_0101_RL_04_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0325_0101_RL_04_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0325_0106_RL_05",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0325_0106_RL_05_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Rimelash_05",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0325_0106_RL_05_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0325_0101_RL_05_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0325_0101_RL_05_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0325_0107_RL_06",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0325_0107_RL_06_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Rimelash_06",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0325_0107_RL_06_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0325_0101_RL_06_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0325_0101_RL_06_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0325_0108_RL_07",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0325_0108_RL_07_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Rimelash_07",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0325_0108_RL_07_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0325_0101_RL_07_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0325_0101_RL_07_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0325_0109_RL_08",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0325_0109_RL_08_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Rimelash_08",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0325_0109_RL_08_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0325_0101_RL_08_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0325_0101_RL_08_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_03_PVP_SpySpot_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_03_PVP_SpySpot_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_03_PVP_PoachSpot_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_03_PVP_PoachSpot_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_03_PVP_ControlSpot_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_03_PVP_ControlSpot_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_03_PVP_SpySpot_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_03_PVP_SpySpot_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_03_PVP_PoachSpot_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_03_PVP_PoachSpot_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_03_PVP_ControlSpot_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_03_PVP_ControlSpot_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_03_PVP_SpySpot_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_03_PVP_SpySpot_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_03_PVP_PoachSpot_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_03_PVP_PoachSpot_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_03_PVP_ControlSpot_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_03_PVP_ControlSpot_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0301_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0301_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0302_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0302_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0303_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0303_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0304_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0304_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0305_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0305_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0306_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0306_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0307_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0307_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0308_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0308_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0309_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0309_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0310_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0310_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0301_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0301_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0302_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0302_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0303_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0303_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0304_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0304_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0305_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0305_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0306_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0306_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0307_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0307_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0308_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0308_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0309_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0309_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0310_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0310_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0301_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0301_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0302_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0302_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0303_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0303_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0304_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0304_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0305_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0305_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0306_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0306_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0307_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0307_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0308_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0308_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0309_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0309_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0310_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0310_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0361_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0361_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0362_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0362_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0363_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0363_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0364_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0364_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0365_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0365_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0366_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0366_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0367_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0367_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0368_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0368_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0369_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0369_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0370_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0370_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0361_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0361_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0362_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0362_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0363_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0363_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0364_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0364_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0365_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0365_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0366_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0366_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0367_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0367_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0368_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0368_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0369_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0369_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0370_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0370_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0361_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0361_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0362_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0362_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0363_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0363_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0364_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0364_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0365_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0365_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0366_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0366_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0367_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0367_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0368_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0368_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0369_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0369_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0370_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0370_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_03_H_01_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_03_H_01_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_03_H_02_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_03_H_02_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_03_H_03_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_03_H_03_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 3,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    }
]